One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Overture
Uvertür
I've gotta save him. I've gotta save him!
Onu kurtarmalıyım.
There are sky sharks!
Burada gökyüzü köpek balıkları var!
Consider this the wrath of God Enel!
Bunu Enel-sama'nın gazabı olarak gör!
After all that, you were no match for us priests.
Gördük ki sen, biz rahiplerin dengi değilsin.
Sky Knight!
Gökyüzü Şövalyesi!
You're a zoan, aren't you?! Are you stupid?
Sen zoan değil misin?! Çıldırdın mı?
Oh, yeah, you're a zoan, too.
Evet, sen de zoansın.
Such an unfortunate weakness...
Zaman kaybı...
Why don't you join your master?!
Efendine katıl!
How absurd!
Ne kadar gülünç!
I can't stand how weak they all are.
Zayıflıklarına tahammül edemiyorum.
Were this river bottomless, perhaps they'd stand a chance.
Nehrin dibi olmasaydı hayatta kalma şansları olurdu ama...
Unfortunately for them, there is a riverbed down there.
ne yazık ki var.
Now then...
Şimdi...
I wonder if the three who escaped have been hunted down yet.
3 kaçak yakalandı mı merak ediyorum.
Is a well really all that strange?
O kuyunun nesi o kadar ilginç?
Yes.
Öyle deme.
It's implausible for it to be wedged under a tree.
Kuyunun ağacın altına sıkışmış olması çok ilginç.
It's as if nature has overtaken civilization here.
Sanki orman, eski bir uygarlığın üzerine yayılmış gibi.
Regardless, if we can't find a way across this river,
Neyse, nehri geçmenin bir yolunu bulamazsak...
we won't be able to get through the forest.
ormandan çıkamayacağız.
Looks like finding that god is out of the question.
O tanrıyı bulma işi yattı galiba.
The civilization couldn't predict the growth of this tree.
Burada yaşayanlar ağacın büyüme hızını hesap edememişler.
I've never seen anything quite like this.
Böylesini ilk defa görüyorum.
Hey, Nami!
Hey, Nami!
Can you see anything from up there?!
Bir şey görebiliyor musun?!
The island where a god lives, Upper Yard...
Tanrının yaşadığı ada, Yukarı Bahçe...
Hey! What are you mumbling up there?!
Hey! Ne mırıldanıyorsun?!
Did you find that god?!
Buldun mu tanrıyı?!
I wonder if she saw something.
Acaba bir şey mi gördü.
This island...
Bu ada...
There's no way!
Mümkün değil!
You're basically finished.
İşiniz bitti.
Hurry up and rest in peace.
Acele edin de selanızı okuyalım.
There's no way you can win against a priest.
Bir rahibe karşı kazanma şansınız yok.
I-I can't go on anymore!
B-Bittim, tükendim!
My heart can't take any more surprises.
Daha fazla sürprizi kalbim kaldırmayacak.
You're all out of options.
Yapacak bir şeyiniz kalmadı.
Your boat has nearly reached the exit of the Lost Woods.
Botunuz, Kayıp Orman'ın çıkışına vardı sayılır.
When that happens, it's all over!
O zaman her şey bitecek!
Unless you learn to fly like a bird,
Kanatlanıp uçmaya başlamadığınız sürece,
you've got no chance of escape.
kaçma şansınız yok.
You'll wander, lost in these woods, until you die of exhaustion!
Bu ormanda çaresizce dolanıp yorgunluktan öleceksiniz!
That's not...
Bu dediklerin...
gonna happen!
olmayacak!
Oh, but it will!
Ah, hayır, olacak!
Surprise Balls:
Sürpriz Toplar:
Ball Dragon!
Ejder Topu!
Now let's have some fun!
Asıl şimdi gösteri başlıyor!
Which one is the firebomb ball?
Acaba hangisi ateş bombası?
If you touch it, there will be an extraordinary explosion!
Dokunursan, devasa bir patlama olacak!
Good! Here's my chance. We can still do this!
Pekâlâ! Şimdi tam zamanı. Hâlâ şansımız var!
I'll leave things here to you, Luffy!
Sen halledersin, Luffy!
Climbing up that tree to escape?
Ağaca tırmanıp kaçacaksın, ha?
How can he read my mind?!
Nasıl oluyor da aklımı okuyor?!
Stop following me!
Bırak peşimi!
Wh-What?!
N-Ne?!
Oh, I see!
Ah, anladım!
It was controlled by this string.
Demek bu ip ile kontrol ediyor.
I'll take care...
Şu ipin...
of this thing!
icabına bakayım!
I can't control the Ball Dragon anymore!
Ejder Topu'nu artık kontrol edemem!
Such insolence!
Bu ne cüret!
Just hang on and come to me!
Gel bakayım bana!
Hey, don't hang on with the other hand, too!
Hey, diğer elini bıraksana!
There it is!
İşte orada!
I was right! That's the exit, no doubt about it!
Haklıymışım! Şüphesiz, işte çıkış!
Of course!
Tabii!
Why didn't I think of this earlier?!
Neden daha önce aklıma gelmedi ki?!
We fell from a high place,
Yüksek bir yerden düştük,
so of course the exit is at the same height!
çıkış da yukarı doğru olmalı!
Now that I know how to get out, the boat rule doesn't matter!
Artık çıkışı bildiğime göre bot yolu önemli değil!
I have to hurry.
Acele etmeliyim.
I'm worried about that huge explosion.
O dev patlama hayra alamet değildi.
They'd better be okay!
Umarım iyilerdir!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ay, ay, ay, ay...
That was close!
Ucuz kurtuldum!
What an unbelievable idiot!
Şu salağın yaptığına inanamıyorum!
No, maybe he decided to take me out with him.
Sanırım beni de kendiyle birlikte öldürmek istedi.
This isn't good. My training is still insufficient!
Bu hiç iyi değil. Antremanlarım yeterli değilmiş.
He completely took control for a second there!
Bir anlığına tüm kontrolü eline aldı!
If such a trivial thing can break my focus,
Böyle eften püften bir şeyin konsantrasyonumu bozması...
it'll hinder my mantra!
mantrama köstek olur!
You're right!
Haklısın!
That was close!
Çok yakındı!
You're still alive?!
Sen hâlâ hayatta mısın?!
Get off of me!
İn üzerimden!
You idiot!
Aptal!
Don't let him go, Luffy! Get off of me!
Bırakma onu, Luffy! Bırak beni!
Hold on tight to that dango!
O tombalağı sakın bırakma!
You–
Sen–
Oh, Sanji! You're alive?!
Oh, Sanji! Hayatta mısın?!
No thanks to you!
Neredeyse o patlamayla ölümüme neden olacaktın!
Pay more attention to others!
Bir şey yapmadan önce düşün!
In any case, dango...
Her neyse, tombalak çocuk;
You keep saying "ordeal of this," "ordeal of that,"
Test mest bir şeyler zırvalayıp duruyorsun,
but frankly, we've done nothing to earn this punishment.
ama açıkçası biz bu cezayı hak etmedik.
And yet, we're going through this stupid sky ordeal...
Ama yine de bu aptal teste katlanıyoruz...
because two helpless ladies...
çünkü iki yardıma muhtaç hanımefendi...
are waiting for me to come to their rescue.
benim onları kurtarmamı bekliyor.
In other words...
Bir başka deyişle...
this is... the Ordeal of Love!
bu "Aşk Testi"!
Is this guy an idiot, too?!
Bu da mı zeka özürlü be?!
I said get off of me!
İn üstümden dedim!
Y-You! You! Dammit! Let me go!
L-Lan! Lan! Lanet olsun! Bırak beni!
Two against one is playing dirty!
İkiye karşı bir, hiç adil değil!
You bastards kidnapped our friends.
Siz şerefsizler arkadaşlarımızı kaçırdınız!
You made a cute angel cry and tried to kill her.
Tatlılar tatlısı bir meleği ağlattınız ve öldürmeye çalıştınız.
You have no right to say we play dirty.
Adil oynamaktan bahsetme bana.
He's right, you know.
Haklı, sen de biliyorsun.
It's amazing that you can predict our movements,
Hamlelerimizi önceden görebiliyor olman şaşırtıcı,
but even so...
ama yine de...
it doesn't mean anything if you can't avoid our attacks, right?
saldırılarımızdan kaçamıyorsan bir anlamı yok, değil mi?
I-Idiots! Stop it!
A-Aptallar! Durun!
I'm one of the priests that serve God!
Ben Tanrı'nın rahiplerinden biriyim!
Let me go!
Bırakın beni!
Hey, are you listening?!
Hey, dinlemiyor musunuz?!
Avoiding a priest's judgment is a first-degree crime in Skypiea!
Bir rahibin hükmüne karşı gelmek Skypiea'da 1. derece bir suçtur!
Listen to me!
Dinleyin beni!
Attacking me is a declaration of war against the almighty God Enel!
Bana saldırmak, yüce Tanrı Enel'e savaş açtığınız anlamına gelir!
Keep your mouth shut, or the flavor will escape!
Ağzını kapalı tut, yoksa aroman kaçacak!
When you prepare pepper for the ultimate mignonette sauce,
Yemeğin sosunu hazırlarken...
the most important step is to strongly, roughly...
en önemli şey, taze baharatları...
and without hesitation crush it into a fine powder.
güzelce ezmektir.
Then, the sublime flavor confined inside will be...
Böylece içlerindeki aroma...
Stop it!
Dur!
Stop it! It's gonna hurt! So stop it!
Dursana! Çok acıyacak! Yapma, dur!
Concassé!
Eziş!
Gan Fall, the former god, went into Upper Yard.
Eski tanrı Gan Fall, Yukarı Bahçe'ye gitti.
What's the matter, Aisa?
Sorun nedir, Aisa?
Two voices went silent.
İki kişinin sesi yok oldu.
What'd you say?!
Ne dedin?!
Is that your mantra?
Mantranla mı hissettin?
Yeah...
Evet...
Just now...
Az önce...
You can tell with your mantra, Aisa?
Mantran öyle mi diyor, Aisa?
Two voices went quiet...
"İki kişinin sesi yok oldu..."
Is that true?!
Öyle mi?!
There's no mistake about it.
Şüphe yok.
You all know that since birth, she's been able to use mantra,
Hepiniz biliyorsunuz ki doğuştan mantra kullanabiliyor.
a mysterious power that allows her to sense people
O gizemli güç ile insanların varlığını...
even from a distance.
uzakta olsalar bile sezebiliyor.
So two voices have gone silent?
Yani iki ses yok oldu mu?
Yes... They disappeared around the same time...
Evet... Aynı anda yok oldular...
I think... Gan Fall and one of the priests...
Sanırım... Gan Fall ve rahiplerden biri...
A mutual kill?!
Birbirlerini mi...?
A good performance from the old man!
Moruğa helal olsun!
That leaves three priests.
Geriye üç rahip kaldı.
This works in our favor.
Bu işimize gelir.
Looks like heaven has answered our prayers.
Görünüşe göre dualarımız kabul oldu.
This is our chance to crush the priests.
Rahipleri ezip geçmemiz için güzel bir fırsat bu.
Yeah!
Evet!
We'll launch an all-out attack on Upper Yard immediately!
Hemen Yukarı Bahçe'ye tüm gücümüzle saldırmalıyız!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
You'll always be nervous around Wyper, huh?
Wyper'ın yanında hep gergin oluyorsun, değil mi?
C'mon, out of the way.
Şimdi, çekil yolumdan.
Ow!
Ah!
Hey, Raki! Wait!
Hey, Raki! Bekle!
What is it?
Ne oldu?
Gan Fall didn't beat that priest.
Rahibi yenen Gan Fall değildi.
There are other people here. They did it.
Başka insanlar var. Onlar yendi.
Other people?
Başka insanlar mı?
Was it those Blue Sea dwellers who entered Skypiea?
Skypiea'ya giren Mavi Deniz insanları mıydı yoksa?
I don't know, but they're definitely scary!
Kimler bilmiyorum ama çok korkunçlar!
So...
O yüzden...
be careful.
dikkatli ol.
Got it.
Anladım.
Aisa, give me your bag.
Aisa, çantanı ver.
What?!
Ne?!
No! This is my secret bag with my treasure inside!
Hayır! Bu benim hazinemi sakladığım gizli çantam!
I know.
Biliyorum.
I'll get some more for you.
Daha fazlasını toplayıp getireceğim.
Really?!
Gerçekten mi?!
Yeah.
Evet.
Huh?
Ha?
I've been rescued?
Hayatta mıyım?
Sky Knight!
Gökyüzü Şövalyesi!
We need a doctor! Wait, that's me!
Doktor lazım! Dur, doktor benim!
Thank goodness... He's still alive.
Şükürler olsun... Hâlâ hayatta.
This is strange, though.
Ama çok garip.
I thought we fell into that river.
Nehre düşmüştük.
I wonder who pulled us out...
Bizim kim çıkardı acaba...
Who's there? Did someone say "god"?
Kim var orada? "Tanrı" mı?
Who just spoke?!
Kim konuştu?!
Huh? What?!
Ha? Ne?!
Spit it out already! What did you see up there?!
Söylesene! Yukarıda ne gördün?!
No more questions. Just follow me!
Soru sorma. Beni takip et!
We have to reach the shore somehow.
Bir şekilde kıyıya ulaşmalıyız.
Hey! Give me a hand!
Hey! Bir yardım etsenize!
How can we follow you if you're behind us?!
Seni takip edeceksek önden gitmen gerekmiyor mu?!
The shore?
Kıyıya mı?
That's right.
Evet.
We need to verify it up close.
Yakınına gidip teyit etmeliyiz,
I'm starting to doubt my own eyes...
çünkü gördüklerime inanamıyorum...
I thought he'd never shut up.
Hiç susmayacak sanmıştım.
Hey!
Hey!
Luffy! Sanji! I found the boat!
Luffy! Sanji! Botu buldum!
Hurry up! Or it'll leave the forest!
Acele edin! Yoksa ormandan çıkacak!
Oh, Usopp's alive.
Ah, Usopp hayattaymış.
Wait, he said the boat's leaving!
Dur, bot gidiyor dedi!
Oh, crap!
Ah, lanet olsun!
It's almost to the stretch that leads to the exit!
Ormandan çıkmasına az kaldı!
Get over here and hold on to me!
Buraya gelin ve bana tutunun.
Hold on to you?
Sana mı tutunalım?
Here goes!
Hadi bakalım!
Usopp...
Usopp...
Aah-eeh-ah-eeh-aaaaah-eeh-ah-eeh-aaaah!
Aah-eeh-aaaaaaaaaaaaaaa-ah!
All right! I got it!
Pekâlâ! Yakaladım!
Yahoo! Usopp's the man!
Yaşasın be! Usopp harikasın!
That hurt! Are you trying to kill me?!
Acıdı lan! Beni öldürmeye mi çalışıyorsun?!
I got excited!
Heyecan yaptım!
You're pretty cool sometimes!
Bazen acayip havalı oluyorsun!
Yeah! You underestimated me, didn't you?!
Evet! Beni hafife aldınız, değil mi?!
Huh?
Ha?
Huh? Huh? Hey! Hey, hey!
Ha? Ha? Hey! Hey, hey!
Hey! W-W-Wait a second!
Hey! D-D-Dur bir saniye!
No... No biggie...
S-S-Sorun yok...
I'll make you pay for this...
Sana bunu ödeteceğim...
It would have been easier for me to stretch here myself...
Kendim uzansam daha kolaydı...
Anyway, we're almost free of the Lost Woods.
Neyse, Kayıp Orman'dan çıkmak üzereyiz.
So Satori has fallen...
Demek Satori yenildi...
What a rookie, letting his mantra falter!
Ne büyük acemilik, mantrasının kontrolünü kaybetmiş!
I believe the illegal entrants are from the Blue Sea this time.
Sanırım bu kez kaçak girenler Mavi Deniz'den.
It seems they're no ordinary people.
Sıradan insanlar değiller gibi.
The sacrifices are roaming free as well...
Sunakta da işler kızışıyor.
However, even if we let them be,
Ancak onları boş versek bile,
they won't manage to find a way off the island.
bu adadan kaçacak bir yol bulamazlar.
More importantly, now...
Daha da önemlisi, şimdi...
"Sky Punk" Gedatsu Skypiean Priest
"Gökyüzü Patronu" Gedatsu Skypiea Rahibi
Do you sense the voice of a sorrowful warrior, Holy?
Hüzünlü bir savaşçının feryadını duyuyor musun, Holy?
No matter how many battles, it's the same result.
Ne kadar savaşırsak savaşalım, sonuç aynı.
Shura defeated Gan Fall, but the Ordeal of Balls was overcome.
Shura, Gan Fall'ı yendi ama Top Testi başarıyla geçildi.
Such a tumultuous day!
Bayağı olaylı bir gün oluyor!
They shall not pass.
Asla buradan geçemeyecekler!
Even attempting to see God is pure insolence.
Tanrı'yı görmeye çalışmak bile büyük hadsizlik.
Though it's nearly sunset, it seems Upper Yard is going to be...
Güneş batmak üzere, Yukarı Bahçe yakında...
"Sky Breeder" Ohm Skypiean Priest
"Gökyüzü Hayvan Terbiyecisi" Ohm Skypiea Rahibi
quite shaken up.
sallanacak.
"Sky Rider" Shura Skypiean Priest
"Gökyüzü Binicisi" Shura Skypiea Rahibi
The fugitives can wait.
Kaçaklar bekleyebilir.
It seems some opponents deserving of my wrath have appeared.
Görünüşe göre gazabımı hak eden yeni rakipler geldi.
Listen up, everyone!
Herkes dinlesin!
Upper Yard is in chaos right now!
Yukarı Bahçe'ye şu an kaos hakim!
This is the opportunity of a lifetime!
Böyle bir fırsatı bir daha yakalayamayız!
We're heading straight for God's Shrine!
Hedefimiz Tanrı'nın Tapınağı!
Do not fear Enel!
Enel'den korkmayın!
Our savior, the almighty Kalgara, shall preserve us!
Şanlı Savaşçı Kalgara'nın ruhu bizi koruyacak!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
Braham!
Braham!
Yeah!
Evet!
Kamakiri!
Kamakiri!
Genbo!
Genbo!
Yeah!
Evet!
Raki!
Raki!
Make it back safe!
Herkes sağ salim dönsün!
We're splitting up here!
Şimdi dağılın!
We swear to the great warrior Kalgara to shine the Light of Shandora!
Şanlı Savaşçı Kalgara'ya yemin olsun, Shandora'nın ışığını yakacağız!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
– So you've come, Shandians!
– Demek geldiniz, Shandialılar!
There's no need to explain, is there?
Açıklamaya gerek yok, değil mi?
Look at this.
Baksanıza.
You recognize this, right?
Tanıdık gelmiyor mu?
What's going on?!
Neler oluyor?!
How did something from below get up here?
Yeryüzünden buraya nasıl gelmiş?
That's the same one, right?
Aynısı, değil mi?
No, it's not.
Hayır, değil.
What?!
Ne?!
This is the other half of the one we saw on the ground.
Bu yeryüzünde gördüğümüzün diğer yarısı.
The other half?!
Diğer yarısı mı?!
It's been bothering me all along.
Bir türlü aklıma yatmıyordu.
This kind of land shouldn't exist in the White-White Sea.
Bu tip toprağın Beyaz-Beyaz Deniz'de olmaması gerekiyor.
From the start, it was strange that this island wasn't made of island clouds.
Başından beri bu adanın bulutlardan yapılmamış olması şüpheliydi.
In other words, the island of Upper Yard...
Bir başka deyişle, bu Yukarı Bahçe denen ada...
originated on the surface below.
yeryüzünden buraya gelmiş.
That house seemed strange to me.
O ev garipti.
There was a second floor, but no stairs to reach it.
İkinci bir katı vardı ama üst kata çıkacak merdivenler yoktu.
Plus, there's no reason to build a house on the water's edge.
Ayrıca uçurumun kenarında olması da saçmaydı.
That seashore was a split in the island!
O kıyı, adanın bir bölümüydü!
A-Amazing!
İ-İnanılmaz!
Idiots! Look closer.
Aptallar! Dikkatli bakın.
A dreamer, huh?
Hayalperest, ha?
He's dreamt up quite the appearance, at least.
En azından gösteriş konusunda hayal gücü genişmiş.
Why?
Ne diyorsun?
What the...?! It's just a board?!
Ne...?! Kartondan mıymış?
This is the other half of that island that was torn away.
Bu parçalanmış adanın diğer yarısı.
This island was part of Jaya!
Bu ada, Jaya'nın bir parçasıydı!
So the island was split in two a long time ago,
O hâlde ada uzun bir süre önce ikiye ayrıldı,
and part of it rose into the sky.
ve bir parçası gökyüzüne doğru yükseldi.
But how could something like that happen?!
Ama böyle bir şey nasıl olabilir?!
There are so many south birds...
Ne kadar çok güney kuşu var...
But why...
Ama neden...
Why are they so big?!
Neden bu kadar büyükler?!
Hey! It's about time you woke up!
Hey! Sonunda uyanabildin!
Is it morning already?
Sabah mı oldu?
That's just like Zoro!
Aynı Zoro bu!
Stay focused, dumbasses!
Biraz tetikte olun, salaklar!
The "City of Gold" that Noland saw...
Bir zamanlar yeryüzünde var olan...
that once existed on the surface...
Noland'ın gördüğü "Altın Şehir"...
It didn't sink into the ocean!
denizin dibini boylamamış!
This part of Jaya...
Jaya'nın kayıp kısmı...
has been in the sky all this time!
bunca zamandır gökyüzündeymiş!